[{"answer": "Probably because I didn't like the way I looked.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Why don't you like your picture?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "You know I had -- I had a really good time.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "What was it like for you last night when you went on there?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Did you feel awkward when that happens?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "I think he was starting to get it.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Do you think -- do you think he got it by the end?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I think he was starting -- yes.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Do you think maybe a few more lessons?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "You know most of the memories that I have of that time was backstage.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "What memories does it bring back to you if anything?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "ONO: No, not at all.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "-- part of a famous family?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "I was -- I mean I guess what you would call a classic tomboy.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "When you can start to remember, what kind of girl were you?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I felt like it wasn't right for me, but at that point I mean, I didn't know -- I didn't know about, you know, being transgender.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Or did you just feel odd?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "No, I don't think it really made it -- I think that was kind of incidental.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Did that make it more difficult for you?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Never, no.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "And you weren't attracted to boys at all?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Just kind of bland, really.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "What was the experience like?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "No, it wasn't -- no.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "To prove to yourself that you'd at least try it?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "It does, but there's an expectation of the girls that I'm going out with, that I'm supposed to act like a girl, too.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Does that feel natural or normal to you at the time?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "At what point does the confusion you have when you think you're a lesbian start to transform into there's something else here?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "For me it was a pretty long process, actually.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "And at what point do you work out what that something else may be?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Nice and flat, huh?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "You know what?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "That is correct, yes.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "That's correct?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "And again, this was over -- we talked about it over time.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "How did she react?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "No, I think she -- I think when I was really young, she thought I was going to grow up and be gay.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Do you think?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Very.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "When you walk around, are people supportive to you?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "It is really.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "I mean that's a remarkable sign of our times, isn't it?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "It feels great, absolutely.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Does that make you feel good?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Well, early on in our relationship, he told me -- actually, I was told by a friend of his that he was indeed transgender.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "You didn't have a clue really, did you?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I compartmentalized it and put it away.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "And what was your honest reaction when he said that?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "It's amazing when I can compartmentalize on that.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "I mean -- that's quite something, to compartmentalize it, is it?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Yes, that's correct.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "The great advantage of having you as his girlfriend is -- I think you're bisexual, right?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "I find him more attractive as a man.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "-- right now is, do you?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "As it was all unfurling, when it came out of its compartmentalization.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "OK, well, there are two components.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Did you have arguments?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Well, emotionally we went through a lot of work.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "What about psychologically?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "For the good.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Well, without being too query here, but it's the kind of question I guess most viewers must be thinking, as your sex life been affected adversely or for the good by all this?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "That's a remarkable thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "It can't always be the case.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Is part of the reason that you feel able to deal with it, Jennifer, that he's happier?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "You know what's going on?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "That's a compliment.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Is that a patronizing thing to say?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "No, I was always Chaz, with you.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Well, I can't blame it solely on Chaz's transition.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Why was that?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Actually, no.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "For you, Chaz, when you saw Jennifer fall off the wagon, did it worry you that perhaps the stress of everything that you had put her through was now coming out in alcohol?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Really good.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "And how are things right now?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Oh, my goodness.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Are you going to get married now?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Can we talk about children?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Sometimes, you know.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "People think I'm a -- idiot, you know?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "No, it was good.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Did it even hurt?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Greater love, there's no woman that can do that, right?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Not so much any more.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Do you ever miss the female Chaz?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Sure, yeah.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "From a technical point of view, are you now a straight guy?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "I'm a bisexual woman.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "And you can't be a lesbian any more, right?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "We amused Dave.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Do you amuse yourselves when you explain all this to people who just sort of can't get it?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "I thought it was great.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "What did you think watching that?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "I would like to.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "Have you talked about it?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "We are, yes.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Are you legally now able to marry as a man and wife?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "I think that we probably will.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "And would you choose to do that?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "There's no ultimatum.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Is there a window here that we're talking about?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "Yeah, it really has -- not to make excuses, but we went through a lot.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Within a year?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "That will be some wedding, don't you think?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "It's funny because we do differ on our -- how we would like to get married.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Have you ever always thought you may do that one day?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I mean, great timing.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "So the obvious question is would you like to do that?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "Wow, you know, I honestly would be deeply honored to do it.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "Should we get to a stage within the year-long window that Chaz has now said he will be held to, and we do get to that church and you are asked formally to be the officiator, would you do it?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "I -- it's so hard to guess how Sonny would have felt about this, you know, any more than anything else, after he's been gone for 13 years.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "Would it be right to assume that he would have been equally tolerant by this turn of events?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "I -- You know, this is family.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Is that an unfair thing of me to observe?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "I don't want to throw out any political terms and label anybody anything here.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Do you hope that the publicity surrounding Chaz's story may lead to a more tolerant, dare I say, liberal attitude towards this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "Absolutely, it does.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 757, "question": "To sum up, love conquers all, right, Chaz?", "qSentId": 756}, {"answer": "We've got a deal, Piers.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "We got a deal?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "Man, it's more than one incident actually.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 798, "question": "What was going on?", "qSentId": 797}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 813, "question": "Is it one of the downsides of fame, that you were talking about?", "qSentId": 812}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "What's your point?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "I think she meant it to a certain extent.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 842, "question": "You don't think she meant it?", "qSentId": 841}, {"answer": "Movie star, actor.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 844, "question": "What does she do for a living?", "qSentId": 843}, {"answer": "An actor.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 846, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 845}, {"answer": "I think, you know, that whole -- people have to live in that world and --", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 849, "question": "You think it was an act?", "qSentId": 848}, {"answer": "Oh, man, 100 percent.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 851, "question": "Are you glad to be out of it?", "qSentId": 850}, {"answer": "It's just pretend.", "docId": "110512pmt", "aSentId": 856, "question": "They are all pretty fake, is that what you're saying?", "qSentId": 855}]